

Navin Hariharan

Cybersecurity & Al Enthusiast

- © Sri Ramachandra Villa, 6/8, Lakshmi nagar 10th street, Nanganallur, Chennai
- **%** +917305574234
- @ navin@navin-hariharan.com
- ø https://navin-hariharan.com/
- ☐ Date of birth: 23 Feb 2003
- Nationality: Indian

Interests

Coding

Travelling

Video Games

Watching Movies

Listening to Music

Projects

Network Mapping Tool May 2020

OSINT FRAMEWORK

Jun 2020

DDOS prevention solution Jan 2022

Jai1 2022

Dreambooth Feb 2023

FED 2023

FLUX LORA Aug 2024

Languages

English



I have a unique passion for technology that drives me, I have accumulated more than **8 years** of experience in the **cybersecurity** domain. In addition to this, I have also accrued **2 years** of knowledge in a relatively newer field such as **Artificial Intelligence**. I head the top managerial level with all executive powers and responsibilities as the CEO of CyberHakz Pvt. Ltd. and Director of Alfa Global Wealth Advisors Pvt. Ltd. I have learned many tools and programming languages such as **Python, SQL, Stable Diffusion, FLUX, OLLAMA** and much more. As a fun fact, I happen to love coding, listening to music and also enjoy driving!!

Profiles

in navin-hariharan

navin-hariharan

o navin_hariharan

Experience

CYBERHAKZ PRIVATE LIMITED

Founder/CEO

https://cyberhakz.com/

Being the **CEO** of <u>CyberHakz Pvt. Ltd.</u> I guide the company and manage operations. I assure top security methods. I also team up for solutions and give our group ideas. I make important choices and support us in growing.

ALFA GLOBAL WEALTH ADVISORS PRIVATE LIMITED

Director

https://alfaglobalwealth.com/

Mar 2021 - Present India

Mar 2021 - Present

India

Education

Ponnaiyah Ramajayam Institute of Science & Technology (PRIST)

72.6%

NARAYANA E-TECHNO SCHOOL - POONAMALLEE

63.60%

58.80%

NARAYANA E-TECHNO SCHOOL - PALLAVARAM

Sep 2020 - Sep 2024Btech - CSE

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020 CBSE 12th

Jun 2017 - Mar 2018 CBSE 10th

Skills

CyberSecurity

nikto, nmap, burpsuite, postman, wifite, metasploit, SET toolkit

Artificial Intelligence Tools

FLUX, runpod, stable diffution, rvc, onnx, ollama, llama, txt2img, img2img, txt2voice, stability ai

Programming: Python

python, coding, backend dev, development, flask, rest api

Linux

bash, kali, parrot, ubuntu, debian

SOL

Certifications

GURUGRAM POLICE CYBERSECURITY INTERNSHIP

Jun 2020

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER (CEH)

May 2021

CompTIA Security+ ce

Nov 2024